Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Annotated, not numbered
      - M-O
        - Mayfield, Curtis - Something to believe in, 1980; SR-25692; Mayfield, Curtis (Box 51)
          Catalog # RS-1-3077; A-side Matrix # RS13077-CT1-AS
          RSO
        - Mayfield, Curtis - Back to the world, 1973; SR-25693; Mayfield, Curtis (Box 51)
          Catalog # CRS 8015; A-side Matrix # CRS-8015-A-2
          Curtom
        - Mayfield, Curtis - Superfly 1990, 1990; SR-25694; Mayfield, Curtis; Ice-T (Box 51)
          Catalog # V-15602; A-side Matrix # V-1-15602-Z2
        - Mayfield, Curtis - Heartbeat, 1979; SR-25695; Mayfield, Curtis (Box 51)
          Catalog # RS-1-3053; A-side Matrix # RS-1-3053-AS-CP
        - Mayfield, Curtis - Take it to the street, 1990; SR-25696; Mayfield, Curtis (Box 51)
          Catalog # CUR 2008; A-side Matrix # CUR-2008A
        - Mazarati - Mazarati, 1986; SR-25697; Mazarati (Box 51)
          Catalog # 1-25368; A-side Matrix # 1-25368-A-RE-1-SR5
        - Mbenza, Syran - Siska, 1986; SR-25698; Mbenza, Syran (Box 51)
          Catalog # 8734; A-side Matrix # SYL 8328 A
          Syllart Records
        - Mboule, Joe - Ebwan na bila, 1979; SR-25699; Mboule, Joe (Box 51)
          Catalog # DPX 824; A-side Matrix # DPX 824A
          Dragon Phénix
        - M.B.T. Soul - Chase!, 1977; SR-25700; M.B.T. Soul (Box 51)
          Catalog # 2393 157; A-side Matrix # 2393 157 1 DA 380 CIDIS
        - MC 900 Foot Jesus - Too bad; Shut up, 1989; SR-25701; MC 900 Foot Jesus; DJ Zero (Box 51)
          Catalog # W1-3032; A-side Matrix # W1 3032 A1
          Nettwerk
          Vancouver, Canada
        - MC Hammer - Let's get it started, 1988; SR-25702; MC Hammer (Box 51)
          Catalog # C1-90924; A-side Matrix # C1-1-90924-Z2
        - MC Lyte - Lyte as a rock, 1988; SR-25703; MC Lyte (Box 51)
          Catalog # DMD 1256; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-56248-56249-1
          First Priority Music
        - MC Lyte - Eyes on this, 1989; SR-25704; MC Lyte (Box 51)
          Catalog # 91304-1; A-side Matrix # ST-FP-897535-A
        - MC Ren - Keep it real, 1996; SR-25705; MC Ren (Box 51)
          Catalog # 88561-6339-1; A-side Matrix # 88561-6339-1A
          Ruthless Records
        - MC Shy-D - Got to be tough, 1987; SR-25706; MC Shy-D (Box 51)
          In same jacket as # SR-25707. 2 copies.
          Catalog # XR-1004; A-side Matrix # XR-104-A
          Luke Skyywalker Records
          Miami, Florida
        - MC Shy-D - Got to be tough, 1987; SR-25707; MC Shy-D (Box 51)
          In same jacket as # SR-25706. 2 copies.
        - MC Shy D - True to the game, 1993; SR-25708; MC Shy D (Box 52)
          In same jacket as # SR-25709. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 12-PO 195; A-side Matrix # 12-PO-195-A
          Wrap Records
          Atlanta, Georgia
        - MC Shy D - True to the game, 1993; SR-25709; MC Shy D (Box 52)
          In same jacket as # SR-25708. 2 copies.
        - MC Solaar - Prose combat (disc one), 1994; SR-25710; MC Solaar (Box 52)
          In same jacket as # SR-25711. Double album.
          Catalog # 697-124 013-1; A-side Matrix # 697-124 013-1A
          Cohiba Records
        - MC Solaar - Prose combat (disc two), 1994; SR-25711; MC Solaar (Box 52)
          In same jacket as # SR-25710. Double album.
          Catalog # 697-124 013-1; A-side Matrix # 697-124 013-1C
        - MC Twist & the Def Squad - Comin' thru like warriors, 1989; SR-25712; MC Twist & the Def Squad (Box 52)
          Catalog # XR-106; A-side Matrix # XR-106-A
        - McCartney, Paul - Tug of war, 1982; SR-25713; McCartney, Paul (Box 52)
          Catalog # AL 37462; A-side Matrix # AL 37462-1G
        - McClain, Marlon - Changes, 1981; SR-25714; McClain, Marlon (Box 52)
          Catalog # F-9606; A-side Matrix # F 9606 A
          Fantasy
          Berkeley, California
        - McClinton, Delbert - From the album "Second Wind"; From the album "Isla", 1978; SR-25715; McClinton, Delbert; Pinera, Mike (Box 52)
          Catalog # CPEP 0002; A-side Matrix # CPE-P0002A-1A
        - McClain, Janice - Janice McClain, 1980; SR-25716; McClain, Janice (Box 52)
          Catalog # MCA-5740; A-side Matrix # MCA5553 FDS-1
          MCA Records
          Universal City, California
        - McClary, Thomas - Thomas McClary, 1984; SR-25717; McClary, Thomas (Box 52)
          Catalog # 6121ML; A-side Matrix # 6121-ML-A-15A Z60
        - McCoy, Van - Rhythms of the world, 1976; SR-25718; McCoy, Van (Box 52)
          Catalog # HL-69014-698; A-side Matrix # HL-69-14 A-1
          H&L Records
          Englewood Cliffs, New Jersey
        - McCoy, Van - Love is the answer, 1974; SR-25719; McCoy, Van; Soul City Symphony (Box 52)
          Catalog # AV-69002-698; A-side Matrix # AV 69-2 A-2
          Avco Records
        - McCrae, George - We did it!, 1978; SR-25720; McCrae, George (Box 52)
          Catalog # TK-610; A-side Matrix # TK-610-A
          TK Records
          Hialeah, Florida
        - McCrae, George - George McCrae, 1978; SR-25721; McCrae, George (Box 52)
          Catalog # TK-608; A-side Matrix # YTK-608-A
        - McCrarys - On the other side, 1979; SR-25722; McCrarys (Box 52)
          Catalog # JR 35556; A-side Matrix # PAL 35556-1D
          Portrait
        - McCrarys - Loving is living, 1977; SR-25723; McCrarys (Box 52)
          Catalog # JR 34764; A-side Matrix # PAL 34764-1C
        - McDaniel, Chris - Try me, 1989; SR-25724; McDaniel, Chris (Box 52)
          Catalog # MJ-7277-0; A-side Matrix # MJ-7277-0AA-RE
          Megajam Records
          Memphis, Tennessee
        - McFadden & Whitehead - Ain't no stoppin' us now, 1979; SR-25725; McFadden & Whitehead (Box 52)
          In same jacket as # SR-25726. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 2Z8 3675; A-side Matrix # PIR AB-2Z8-3075-3
          Philadelphia International Records
        - McFadden & Whitehead - Ain't no stoppin' us now, 1979; SR-25726; McFadden & Whitehead (Box 52)
          In same jacket as # SR-25725. 2 copies.
        - McFadden & Whitehead - Do you want to dance, 1979; SR-25727; McFadden & Whitehead (Box 52)
          Catalog # AS 633; A-side Matrix # PIR XSS-166275-1AX
        - McGilpin, Bob - Bob McGilpin, 1980; SR-25728; McGilpin, Bob (Box 52)
          Catalog # NBLP 7230; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7230AS-BW2 RE-1
        - McGloiry, Michael - Won't you let me be the one, 1980; SR-25729; McGloiry, Michael (Box 52)
          Catalog # AW12-94964; A-side Matrix # ASM-32353-RE-1
          Airwave Records
        - McGriff, Jimmy - The mean machine, 1976; SR-25730; McGriff, Jimmy (Box 52)
          Catalog # GM-3311; A-side Matrix # GM3311A-1
          Groove Merchant
        - Mc Lane Explosion - Pulstar, 1977; SR-25731; Mc Lane Explosion (Box 52)
          Catalog # TA 4702; A-side Matrix # TA-4702-A-XP
          Tom N' Jerry Records
        - McNally, Larry John - Larry Joh McNally, 1981; SR-25732; McNally, Larry John (Box 52)
          Catalog # ARC 37455; A-side Matrix # PAL 37455-1D
        - McPhatter, Clyde - Welcome home, 1970; SR-25733; McPhatter, Clyde (Box 52)
          Catalog # DL 75231; A-side Matrix # 7 12508
          Decca
        - Mad Dog - Take my love; The feelings of house, 1997; SR-25734; Mad Dog; MD 20/20 (Box 52)
          Catalog # AWX 008; A-side Matrix # HAL 12791-A
          Afro Wax Records
          South Beach, Florida
        - Meadows - The Meadows, 1981; SR-25735; Meadows (Box 52)
          Catalog # RR 19305; A-side Matrix # ST-RR-814735-A
          Radio Records
        - Meco - Music from Star Trek and the Black Hole, 1980; SR-25736; Meco (Box 52)
          Catalog # NBLP 7196; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7196-AS-GD1
        - Meco - Impressions of An American Werewolf in London, 1981; SR-25737; Meco (Box 52)
          Catalog # NBLP 7260; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7260 BS PNC-C-1-1-1
        - Meco - Devil delight, 1979; SR-25738; Meco (Box 52)
          Catalog # NBD 20196; A-side Matrix # NBD-290196-AS-CP1
        - Medicine - The Medicine EP, 1997; SR-25739; Medicine (Box 52)
          In same jacket as # SR-25740. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 12 NEXT 011; A-side Matrix # NEXT 011-A1
          Next Century Records
        - Medicine - The Medicine EP, 1997; SR-25740; Medicine (Box 52)
          In same jacket as # SR-25739. 2 copies.
        - Mehta, Zubin - Mehta bolero, sensational orchestral showpieces, 1972; SR-25741; Mehta, Zubin; Los Angeles Philharmonic (Box 52)
          Catalog # CS 7132; A-side Matrix # ZAL 11450
          London Records
        - Mekon - Phatty's lunchbox, 1997; SR-25742; Mekon (Box 52)
          Catalog # WALLT 032; A-side Matrix # WALL T 032-A1
          Wall of Sound
        - Mekon - Welcome to Tackletown (disc one), 1997; SR-25743; Mekon (Box 52)
          In same jacket as # SR-25744. Double album.
          Catalog # WALLLP006; A-side Matrix # WALL LP 006-A1
        - Mekon - Welcome to Tackletown (disc two), 1997; SR-25744; Mekon (Box 52)
          In same jacket as # SR-25743. Double album.
          Catalog # WALLLP006; A-side Matrix # WALL LP 006-C1
        - Mekon - Welcome to Tackletown, 1996; SR-25745; Mekon (Box 52)
          Catalog # WALL T 023; A-side Matrix # WALL T 023 A1
        - Mekon - Revenge of the Mekon (remix), 1995; SR-25746; Mekon (Box 52)
          Catalog # WALLT012R; A-side Matrix # WALL T 012 R-A1
        - Melaaz - Melaaz (disc one), 1995; SR-25747; Melaaz (Box 52)
          In same jacket as # SR-25748. Double album.
          Catalog # 74321279491; A-side Matrix # 74321-27949-1A
          BMG
          Germany
        - Melaaz - Melaaz (disc two), 1995; SR-25748; Melaaz (Box 52)
          In same jacket as # SR-25747. Double album.
          Catalog # 74321279491; A-side Matrix # 74321-27949-1C
        - Melanie - Ballroom streets (disc one), 1978; SR-25749; Melanie (Box 52)
          In same jacket as # SR-25750. Double album.
          Catalog # TOM-2-9003; A-side Matrix # TOM-2-9003-A1
          Tomato
        - Melanie - Ballroom streets (disc two), 1978; SR-25750; Melanie (Box 52)
          In same jacket as # SR-25749. Double album.
          Catalog # TOM-2-9003; A-side Matrix # TOM-2-9003-C1
        - Melendez, Lisette - Goody goody, 1993; SR-25751; Melendez, Lisette (Box 52)
          In same jacket as # SR-25752. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 659965 6; A-side Matrix # 01 659965 20 1A1
          Fever Records
          Yonkers, New York
        - Melendez, Lisette - Goody goody, 1993; SR-25752; Melendez, Lisette (Box 52)
          In same jacket as # SR-25751. 2 copies.
        - Melody - Brown sugar, 1981; SR-25753; Melody (Box 52)
          Catalog # B,s R 1001; A-side Matrix # BS-2057-A
          B's Records
        - Melvin, Harold - All things happen in time, 1981; SR-25754; Melvin, Harold; Blue Notes (Box 52)
          Catalog # MCA-5261; A-side Matrix # MCA-2726-A-FLW1
        - Memphis Bleek - Do my...; I get high, 2001; SR-25755; Memphis Bleek (Box 52)
          Catalog # 314 572 762-1; A-side Matrix # DEFR-15228-1-A1
          Roc-A-Fella Records
        - Men at Play - Dr. Jam (in the slam), 1983; SR-25756; Men at Play (Box 52)
          Catalog # SG-809-12; A-side Matrix # SG-809-12-BS
          Sunshine Recordings
          Philadelphia, Pennsylvania
        - Men Without Hats - Where do the boys go? (extended version), 1984; SR-25757; Men Without Hats (Box 52)
          Catalog # TAK 15/12; A-side Matrix # TAK 1512 A-2U-1-1
          Statik Records
          Glasgow, United Kingdom
        - Menajahtwa - La la la, 1994; SR-25758; Menajahtwa (Box 52)
          Catalog # RPROLP 0285; A-side Matrix # RPROLP-0285-A
        - Merchant - Rock it, 1985; SR-25759; Merchant (Box 52)
          Catalog # BENMAC 0051; A-side Matrix # 001-A
          Kalico Records
        - Merchant - Ah coming too, 1987; SR-25760; Merchant (Box 52)
          Catalog # GS2273; A-side Matrix # GS-2273 A
          Straker's Records
        - Merchant - Innervisions, 1989; SR-25761; Merchant (Box 53)
          Catalog # OPI-0-006L; A-side Matrix # OPI-0-006L-A
          Oscar's Production Inc.
        - Meters - Trick bag, 1976; SR-25762; Meters (Box 53)
          Catalog # K 54078; A-side Matrix # K-54078 A1
          Reprise Records
        - Method Actors - Commotion, 1981; SR-25763; Method Actors (Box 53)
          Catalog # P2004; A-side Matrix # 12009 A1
          Press Records
        - Metro - America in my head, 1981; SR-25764; Metro (Box 53)
          Catalog # POSPX 280; A-side Matrix # POSPX280 A
        - Metro LA - The thinka, 1996; SR-25765; Metro LA (Box 53)
          Catalog # HARD17 12; A-side Matrix # HARD 1712-A1
          Concrete
        - Metro LA - O.S.T., 1997; SR-25766; Metro LA (Box 53)
          Catalog # B-014; A-side Matrix # LX-014-A
          Bassex Records
          Redondo Beach, California
        - Michael, George - Too funky, 1992; SR-25767; Michael, George (Box 53)
          Catalog # 44 74352; A-side Matrix # XSS74352A-1A
        - Michaels, Lee - Space and first takes, 1972; SR-25768; Michaels, Lee (Box 53)
          Catalog # SP-4336; A-side Matrix # A+M SP4571-P1
        - Michaels, Margo - Margo Michaels and NiteLite, 1981; SR-25769; Michaels, Margo; NiteLite (Box 53)
          Catalog # RW 32-105; A-side Matrix # ST-RW-814689-A
          Real World Records
        - Michele - Magic love, 1977; SR-25770; Michele (Box 53)
          Catalog # WES 103; A-side Matrix # WE 103A
          West End Records
        - Michie Mee - Victory is calling; On this mic, 1988; SR-25771; Michie Mee; LA Luv (Box 53)
          Catalog # DMD 1263; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-56294-56295-3
        - Michigan & Smiley - Downpression, 1982; SR-25772; Michigan & Smiley (Box 53)
          Catalog # GREL 42; A-side Matrix # CGR 42 A
          Greensleeves Records
          Canada
        - Michigan & Smiley - Sugar daddy, 1983; SR-25773; Michigan & Smiley (Box 53)
          Catalog # RAS 3004; A-side Matrix # RAS-3004-A
          Real Authentic Sound
          Washington, DC
        - Mico Wave - Cookin' from the inside out!!!, 1987; SR-25774; Mico Wave (Box 53)
          Catalog # C 40909; A-side Matrix # PAL-40909 1A
        - Midfield General - Worlds; Bung, 1995; SR-25775; Midfield General (Box 53)
          In same jacket as # SR-25776. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SKINT 4; A-side Matrix # SKINT+4+A
          Skint
          Brighton, United Kingdom
        - Midfield General - Worlds; Bung, 1995; SR-25776; Midfield General (Box 53)
          In same jacket as # SR-25775. 2 copies.
        - Midnight Rhythm - Midnight Rhythm, 1978; SR-25777; Midnight Rhythm (Box 53)
          Catalog # SD 19214; A-side Matrix # STA-784203-B
        - Midnight Star - No parking on the dance floor, 1983; SR-25778; Midnight Star (Box 53)
          Catalog # 60241-1; A-side Matrix # ST-E60241A-3
          Solar
        - Midnight Star - Standing together, 1981; SR-25779; Midnight Star (Box 53)
          In same jacket as # SR-25780. Different discs.
          Catalog # S-19; A-side Matrix # S-19-A
        - Midnight Star - Tuff, 1981; SR-25780; Midnight Star (Box 53)
          In same jacket as # SR-25779. Different discs.
          Catalog # AS-11531; A-side Matrix # AM-11531-A
        - Midtown Funk Allstarz - Who cuts the funk; A little suttin, 1999; SR-25781; Midtown Funk Allstarz; Phunkae (Box 53)
          Catalog # FUNK-002; A-side Matrix # S-42828
          Funk Dawg Records
        - Mighty Fire - I could write a love song, 1981; SR-25783; Mighty Fire (Box 53)
          Catalog # AS-11521; A-side Matrix # AS-11521-A-SP
        - Mighty Hannibal - Hannibalism!, 2001; SR-25784; Mighty Hannibal (Box 53)
          Catalog # ED-290; A-side Matrix # ED-290-A
          Norton Records
        - Mighty High - Mighty High, 1979; SR-25785; Mighty High (Box 53)
          Catalog # MCA-3186; A-side Matrix # MCA-1983
        - Mighty Pope - Sway, 1979; SR-25786; Mighty Pope (Box 53)
          Catalog # RFC 3310; A-side Matrix # RFC-1-3310-LW2
          Warner Bros Records
        - Mighty Swallow - First take, 1984; SR-25787; Mighty Swallow (Box 53)
          Catalog # SCR 345; A-side Matrix # SCR-345-A
          Charlie's Records
        - Mike & Charlie - Body rock, 1997; SR-25788; Mike & Charlie (Box 53)
          Catalog # JFR 009; A-side Matrix # JFR-009-9808X57-A
          Just Funkin Records
          Sarasota, Florida
        - Mikki - Itching for love, 1982; SR-25789; Mikki (Box 53)
          Catalog # EIR-101; A-side Matrix # EIR-101-A
          Emerald International Records
        - Mikki Bleu - I promise, 1989; SR-25790; Mikki Bleu (Box 53)
          Catalog # E1-91171; A-side Matrix # E1-2-91171-Z3
          EMI
        - Miles, Arthur - Trippin' on your love; Helping hand, 1990; SR-25791; Miles, Arthur (Box 53)
          Catalog # FXDJ 148; A-side Matrix # FXDJ-148-A
          FFRR
        - Miles, Buddy - Sneak attack (disc one), 1981; SR-25792; Miles, Buddy; Buddy Miles Regiment (Box 53)
          In same jacket as # SR-25793. Double album.
          Catalog # SD 2-4000; A-side Matrix # STA-814717 A F1
        - Miles, Buddy - Sneak attack (disc two), 1981; SR-25793; Miles, Buddy; Buddy Miles Regiment (Box 53)
          In same jacket as # SR-25792. Double album.
          Catalog # SD 2-4000; A-side Matrix # STA-814719 A F1
        - Milian, Christina - It's about time (disc one), 2004; SR-25794; Milian, Christina (Box 53)
          In same jacket as # SR-25795. Double album.
          Catalog # B0002223-01; A-side Matrix # B0002223-01 LP1 A
        - Milian, Christina - It's about time (disc two), 2004; SR-25795; Milian, Christina (Box 53)
          In same jacket as # SR-25794. Double album.
          Catalog # B0002223-01; A-side Matrix # B0002223-01 LP2 A
        - Miller, Steve - Macho city, 1981; SR-25796; Miller, Steve; Steve Miller Band (Box 53)
          In same jacket as # SR-25797. Different discs.
          Catalog # SPRO-9734; A-side Matrix # SPRO-1-9734
        - Miller, Steve - Circle of love, 1981; SR-25797; Miller, Steve; Steve Miller Band (Box 53)
          In same jacket as # SR-25796. Different discs.
          Catalog # ST-12121; A-side Matrix # ST-1-12121 F4
        - Milli Vanilli - Blame it on the rain, 1989; SR-25798; Milli Vanilli (Box 53)
          Catalog # COOLX 180; A-side Matrix # COOLX 180 A3
          Cooltempo
        - Milli Vanilli - All or nothing, 1988; SR-25799; Milli Vanilli (Box 53)
          Catalog # CTLP 11; A-side Matrix # CTLP 11 COOL A-1
        - Mills, Stephanie - Sweet sensation, 1977; SR-25800; Mills, Stephanie (Box 53)
          In same jacket as # SR-25801. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TCD-106; A-side Matrix # TCD 106 AS A 1S
          20th Century Fox Records
        - Mills, Stephanie - Sweet sensation, 1977; SR-25801; Mills, Stephanie (Box 53)
          In same jacket as # SR-25800. 2 copies.
          Catalog # TCD-106; A-side Matrix # TCD 106 AMC 1S
        - Ming & FS - Face down EP, 1999; SR-25802; Ming & FS (Box 53)
          Catalog # JSK147; A-side Matrix # JSK-147A-1A
          Jungle Sky
        - Ministry - All day; Everyday (is Halloween), 1985; SR-25803; Ministry (Box 53)
          Catalog # WAX 007; A-side Matrix # WAX-007-A
          Wax Trax! Records
        - Mink DeVille - Coup de grâce, 1981; SR-25804; Mink DeVille (Box 53)
          Catalog # SD 19311; A-side Matrix # STA-814773-E
        - Missing Links - Monkey breaks volume 1, 1997; SR-25805; Missing Links (Box 53)
          Catalog # L-48158; A-side Matrix # L-48158
          Primeight Records
        - Mission - Search, 1987; SR-25806; Mission (Box 53)
          Catalog # C 40759; A-side Matrix # AL-40759
        - Mix Master Mike - Anti-theft device (disc one), 1998; SR-25807; Mix Master Mike (Box 53)
          In same jacket as # SR-25808. Double album.
          Catalog # ASP 0985; A-side Matrix # ASP-0985 A1
          Asphodel
        - Mix Master Mike - Anti-theft device (disc two), 1998; SR-25808; Mix Master Mike (Box 53)
          In same jacket as # SR-25807. Double album.
          Catalog # ASP 0985; A-side Matrix # ASP-0985 C1
        - Mizell, Rocky - Let's go dancing; I don't care what you say (I'm gonna love you tonight), 1980; SR-25809; Mizell, Rocky (Box 53)
          Catalog # TKD-443; A-side Matrix # TKD-443-A
          T.K. Disco
        - Mizz - Mizz, 1980; SR-25810; Mizz (Box 53)
          Catalog # NBLP 7204; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7204-AS-RE1-K2
        - Mob Guys - Let the music, 1995; SR-25811; Mob Guys (Box 53)
          Catalog # JCL-0078; A-side Matrix # JCL-0078-A
          Groove Nation Records
        - Modern Romance - Can you move, 1981; SR-25812; Modern Romance (Box 53)
          Catalog # DMD 293; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-40376-1
        - Mondo Rock - Mondo Rock chemistry, 1981; SR-25813; Mondo Rock (Box 53)
          Catalog # SD 19337; A-side Matrix # ST-A-81486-A
        - Monet - Leave the lights on, 1987; SR-25814; Monet (Box 53)
          Catalog # LIG-5701; A-side Matrix # LIG-5701-A
          Ligosa Records
        - T.S. Monk - More of the good life, 1981; SR-25815; T.S. Monk (Box 54)
          Catalog # WTG 19324; A-side Matrix # ST-WTG-81415-C
          Mirage
        - T.S. Monk - House of music, 1980; SR-25816; T.S. Monk (Box 54)
          Catalog # WTG 19291; A-side Matrix # ST-WTG-804603-A
        - Mono Blanco - Product, 1997; SR-25817; Mono Blanco (Box 54)
          In same jacket as # SR-25818. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SM-9067-0; A-side Matrix # SM-9067-A
          Sm:)e Communications
        - Mono Blanco - Product, 1997; SR-25818; Mono Blanco (Box 54)
          In same jacket as # SR-25817. 2 copies.
        - Monster Orchestra - Hangin' out, 1981; SR-25819; Monster Orchestra; Davis, John (Box 54)
          Catalog # GNPS 12005; A-side Matrix # GNPS-12005-A
          GNP Crescendo
        - Montana - I love music; You know how good it is, 1978; SR-25820; Montana (Box 54)
          Catalog # ST-DSKO-36511; A-side Matrix # ST-36511-1
        - Montana Rangers - Pitch black, 2002; SR-25821; Montana Rangers (Box 54)
          Catalog # ZONE 050; A-side Matrix # ZONE 050-A-SR
          Zone Records
          Orlando, Florida
        - Machel - Any minute now, 1999; SR-25822; Machel; Xtatik (Box 54)
          Catalog # VPRL 1548; A-side Matrix # VPRL 1548-A
          VP Records
          Jamaica, New York
        - Monte - Summer jam, 1987; SR-25823; Monte (Box 54)
          Catalog #; A-side Matrix # 8705X06-A
          Slip-Disc Records
          New Jersey
        - Moore, Jackie - I'm on my way, 1979; SR-25824; Moore, Jackie (Box 54)
          Catalog # JC 35991; A-side Matrix # AL-35991-1B
        - Moore, Melba - Never say never, 1983; SR-25825; Moore, Melba (Box 54)
          Catalog # ST-12305; A-side Matrix # ST-1-12305
        - Moore, Melba - Mind up tonight, 1982; SR-25826; Moore, Melba (Box 54)
          Catalog # SPRO-9859; A-side Matrix # SPRO-9859-98483-Z1
        - Morgan, Lee - Search for the new land, 1964; SR-25827; Morgan, Lee (Box 54)
          Catalog # BLP 4169; A-side Matrix # BIULP-4169 D
          Blue Note
        - Morissette, Alanis - Jagged little pill, 1995; SR-25828; Morissette, Alanis (Box 54)
          Catalog # 9362-45901-1; A-side Matrix # 936 245901-1-A
          Maverick
        - Morningstar - Venus, 1979; SR-25829; Morningstar (Box 54)
          Catalog # JC 35713; A-side Matrix # PAL-35713-1D
        - Moroder, Giorgio - E=MC², 1979; SR-25830; Moroder, Giorgio (Box 54)
          Catalog # NBLP 7169; A-side Matrix # NBLP-7169-AS-RE-1
        - Morrison, Jesse - The versatility of Jesse Morrison, 1975; SR-25831; Morrison, Jesse (Box 54)
          Catalog # ABET 408; A-side Matrix # ABET-408-A
        - Moses, Pablo - Pave the way, 1981; SR-25832; Moses, Pablo (Box 54)
          Catalog # MLPS 9633; A-side Matrix # MLPS-9633-A-CP2